'센트럴 퍼크'
모니카?
네 차좀 빌려줄래?
Monica?
Hey, can I borrow the Porsche?
- 그래
- 잘됐다!
- Okay.
- All right!
그런데 그안에서
뭘하면 안된다구?
But what is it not?
여자친구랑 재미보면 안돼
A place to entertain my lady friends.
- 또 뭘하면 안되지?
- 스파게티 먹으면 안돼
- And what else is it not?
- A place to eat spaghetti.
잘했어
차로 어디가려구?
Very good. What do you need
it for anyway?
파워볼 로또 당첨금이
3억 달러래!
The Powerball lottery
is up to 300 million..
- 뉴욕에서는 안판다고 해서..
- 코네티컷까지 가서 사오려구?
- and they don't sell tickets here.
- So you're driving up to Connecticut?
맞아, 코네티컷!
웨스트버지니아 말고
Yeah, Connecticut.
Not West Virginia.
내가 운전할게 같이 가자
나도 로또 사고 싶어
Maybe I'll drive you up there.
I'd like to buy some tickets myself.
챈들러가 수입이 없으니까
3억 달러가 아주 유용할거야
Yeah, with Chandler not getting paid,
we could really use $300 million.
내가 옛날 회사 계속 다녔으면
3억달러? 코방귀도 안뀌었겠지
Yes, because if I was at my old job,
we'd say, "300 million? No, thank you."
- 내것도 사다줄래?
- 나도
- Will you get me tickets too?
- Yeah, me too.
- 좋아
- 이러면 어떨까?
- Sure.
- I have an idea.
각자 50달러씩 모아
로또를 사서
Why don't we all pitch in 50 bucks,
we'll pool our money together..
- 당첨되면 당첨금을 나누는 거야
- 그거 좋겠다!
- and then if we win, we'll split it.
- That's a great idea!
난 빼줘
No, thanks.
- 로또 당첨되고 싶지 않아?
- 물론
- You don't wanna win the lottery?
- Sure I do.
나도 왕이 되고 싶고
I also want to be king
of my own country..
에어하트의
수수께끼도 풀고싶어
and find out what happened
to Amelia Earhart.
- 아직도 그 얘기냐?
- 바람처럼 사라졌단 말야!
- Still on Amelia Earhart?
- The woman just vanished!
농담하지 말고
정말 로또 안살거야?
Seriously, you don't want in on this?
로또 당첨될 확률이
얼만지 알아?
No. Do you know what your odds
are of winning the lottery?
번개에 42번 맞을 확률이
더 높다구
I mean, you have a better chance
of being struck by lightning 42 times.
우린 6명이니까 7번씩만
번개 맞으면 되겠네
But there's six of us, so we'd
only have to get struck 7 times.
이 확률이 훨씬 마음에 든다!
I like those odds!
복권에 250달러나 쓴다니
정말 이해가 안간다
Seriously, you guys, I can't believe
you're gonna spend $250 on the lottery.
그건 정말 '멍멍한 짓'이야
I mean, that's such a bunch
of boo-hockey.
내가 물어볼게
I'll ask.
'멍멍한 짓'?
"Boo-hockey"?
엠마가 말을 하기 시작해서
Oh, we think Emma's about
to start talking..
요즘 말조심하고 있거든
so we're trying to be careful about
what words we use in front of her.
'멍멍한 짓', '빌어 잡수실!'
So get ready to hear a lot
of boo-hockey..
'강아지 같은 분!' 이렇게 말야
gosh darn it
and brother pucker.
말하기 시작했다는걸
어떻게 알아?
How do you know
she's gonna start talking?
요즘 내가 얘기하면
꼭 알아듣는것 같거든
When I talk to her, I almost feel
like she understands what I'm saying.
조이랑 비슷하네
Kind of like Joey.
뭐라구?
What's that now?
프렌즈 시즌 9
'로또 광풍!'
이 로또 표좀 봐!
흥분되는데!
God, look at all these tickets.
It's so exciting.
6학년때 이후로 상 같은거
타본적 없거든!
I haven't won anything
since sixth grade.
파이 먹기 대회 말이지?
Pie-eating contest?
뚱보는 그런일 아니면
상 못탔을 거라 그거지?
You assume because I was heavy that's
the only way I could win something?
아니, 블루베리 범벅이된
자기 사진 봤거든
No, I saw a picture
of you covered in blueberries.
그때 정말 행복했어!
- That was a good day.
- Yeah.
네 차 견인되고 있어!
네 차 끌려간다구!
- They're towing your car!
- I'm parked in a garage on Morton.
난 주차장에 주차했는데?
그럼 다른 차인가 보다!
They're towing a car.
눈에서 별이 보이네!
And I am seeing spots.
엠마는? 여기도 없는데!
Ross, you don't have Emma!
Rachel, you don't have Emma!
- 엠마 어딨어? 어떻게 된거야?
- 진정해
- Where's Emma? Who has Emma?
- Joey, relax.
우리 엄마가 두시간 전에
데려가셨어, 너도 봤잖아!
My mother picked her up two hours ago.
You were there.
- 내가?
- 울 엄마랑 얘기도 했잖아
- I was?
- Yes, and you talked to her.
- 그랬어?
- 엄마가 카세롤 요리 떨어뜨리셨잖아
- I did?
- She dropped off a casserole.
아, 그 아주머니!
Oh, yeah, the casserole lady.
우리가 돈벼락 맞는거
구경하려고 온거야?
Did you come by to watch
us win the big bucks?
그래, 너희들이 당첨되면
모두 발코니로 나가자
Yeah. And then I figured after you win,
we can all go out to the balcony..
한밤중에 무지개 위에서 요정이
춤추는 것도 구경할수 있을거야
and see a night rainbow
with gremlins dancing on top of it.
받지마! 내가 받을거야!
내가 받을거야!
Don't touch the phone!
I'll get it!
- 손은 씻고 나온걸까?
- 여보세요?
- You think he washed his hands?
- Hello?
- 찰리! 어떻게 됐어?
- 무슨 일이야?
- Hey, Charlie, what do you know?
- What's going on?
광고회사에 정식으로
채용될지 알아보는 거야
Chandler's supposed to find out
if he's getting a job at his agency.
인턴사원 15명중에
3명만 뽑는대
But out of 15 interns,
they're only hiring three.
- 와, 경쟁률 세다!
- 그래
- Tough odds.
- Yeah.
너희들 로또만큼 확률이 높으면
좋을텐데, 그치?
If only it were a sure thing
like your 24-state lottery.
너도 드디어 우리편이 됐구나!
Yeah, look who's coming around!
젠장!
다른소식 있으면 전화해줘
Damn it. All right, call me
when you know more.
- 됐어?
- 자리 하난 정해졌대
- Did you get it?
- One of the slots got filled.
- 그게 너야?
- 내 목소리 들으면 몰라?!
- By you?
- Sense the tone.
- 네이트라는 녀석이 차지했어!
- 걔 정말 재수 없어!
- No, that kid Nate got it.
- Oh, I hate that guy.
제발 바지좀
치켜올리라고 해!
I mean, come on, kid,
pull up your pants!
아직 두자리 남은거지?
Well, there's two spots left, right?
그래, 꼭 뽑혔으면 좋겠어
Yeah. I mean, I want this so much.
I wanna get one.
나머지 두자리는 나랑
내친구 찰리가 되면 좋겠다
I want my friend Charlie
to get one.
사실 찰리는 되건 말건
상관없어
Except I don't care about Charlie.
- 안녕!
- 어서와
- Hey, you guys.
- Hey!
굉장한 일이 있었어!
점쟁이가
You are not gonna believe this.
I just saw my psychic..
나더러 오늘
로또 당첨될 거래!
and she said I was definitely
gonna win the lottery tonight!
나도 우리 행운 점쳐볼겸
I thought we could use
some extra luck..
식당에서 위시본 가져왔어!
so I brought a wishbone home
from work.
점쟁이에 위시본까지?
A psychic and a wishbone?
Guys, give someone else a chance.
아이구, 그럼 너희들이
당첨되는게 확실하겠네!
- 누가 해볼래?
- 내가 할까?
- All right, who wants to do it?
- Can I?
채식주의자는
위시본 볼일이 없거든
Vegetarians never get
to do the wishbone.
불공평해
육식을 하지 않는다는 이유로
It's really not fair. Just because
we don't eat the meat..
동물 뼈로 장난도 못치다니!
doesn't mean we don't like
to play with the carcasses.
레이첼, 해볼래?
All right. Rach?
됐어, 손에 칠면조 냄새
묻히고 싶지 않아
I don't want that turkey smell
all over my hands.
내가 할래! 그거하면
카세롤 냄새가 없어질 거야
I'll do it! It'll get the casserole
stink off of mine.
- 내가 이겼음 좋겠다!
- 누가 이기면 어때?
- I hope I win.
- Well, it doesn't really matter.
둘다 같은 소원을 빌거잖아
You're both wishing
for the same thing.
난 무슨 소원 빌건지 말 안할거야
말하면 효력이 없어지거든
I can't tell you what I'm wishing for,
or else, you know, it won't come true.
맞아, 그래도
네 소원이 뭔지 우린 다알아
Right. But we know
what you're wishing for.
- 난 말 안할거라니까!
- 알았어
- I can't really say.
- I understand.
하지만 우리가 생각하는
그 소원 빌거잖아, 그렇지?
But you're wishing
for what we think, aren't you?
거참, 되게 성가시게 구네!
I'm not really comfortable
with these questions!
- 그냥해!
- 빨리 하기나해!
- Please!
- Just do it!
좋아
하나, 둘, 셋!
Okay. One, two, three.
내가 이겼다!
I won! Hey!
네 소원이 꼭 이루어지길 바란다
You know what? I'm sure your
wish is gonna come true.
그래도 혹시 안되면 이 램프를 문질러서
요정 지니를 불러내라구, 악!
But, you guys, just in case, maybe a
genie will come out if we rub this lamp.
왜 이렇게 뜨거워!
That thing gets hot!
그렇게 자꾸 빈정대다가
Ross, just keep making your jokes.
우리가 정말로 당첨되면
어쩌려고 그래?
How are you gonna feel
if we actually do win?
- 너희는 당첨 안돼
- 가능성은 물론 희박하지
- You're not gonna win.
- I know the odds are against us..
하지만 누군가는 탈거 아냐?
그게 우리가 될수도 있어!
but somebody has to win, and it could
be us. And then how you gonna feel?
그러면 기분이 어떨것 같아?
우리 모두 헬리콥터 타고
놀러갈 때
We're gonna be like, "Everybody, let's
take our helicopters up to the Cape."
자기 혼자 그러겠네?
"난 차에"
And you're gonna be all,
like, "Oh, I can't, guys.
"기름 넣고 갈테니까
거기서 만나자"
I'll have to meet you up there.
I gotta gas up the Hyundai."
내 목소리 녹음해서 들어봤는데
하나도 안똑같아!
Okay, I've heard myself on tape,
and I sound nothing like that.
신문 머릿기사가 눈에 훤하다!
"로또 당첨자들의 친구"
I can see the headline now:
"Lottery Winners' Friend..
"가슴 치며 자기 팔 물어뜯다"
Filled With Regret,
Eats Own Arm."
내가 왜
내 팔을 물어뜯냐?!
Why would I eat my own arm?
우린 신문사도 살거니까
우리 마음대로 기사 쓸거야!
Well, you wouldn't, but we own the paper.
We can print whatever we want.
오빠, 내가 오빠 몫으로
50달러 낼께
You know what? I'm gonna
throw in 50 bucks for you.
- 왜?
- 오빠가 로또를
- Why?
- Because I know that you think..
얼마나 '멍멍한 짓'으로
생각하는지 알아
that the lottery is boo-hockey..
하지만 우리 모두 모여서
번호 맞추며 즐거운 시간 보낼텐데
but we're all here, and we're gonna
watch the numbers and have fun.
오빠도 우리랑 함께
했으면 좋겠어
And you're my brother,
and I want you to be a part of this.
그럴 필요없어
내몫은 내가 낼께
You don't have to do that.
I mean, I'll pay for myself.
어쨌든 나도 함께 하길
바라는 네 마음 너무 고맙다
But just the fact that you want me to
have fun with you guys, that's so sweet.
이리와
Come here.
아예 방을 잡아라
Get a room.
만약 당첨되면 넌 어떡할래?
So now that you're in,
what are you gonna do if we win?
- 글쎄, 난 아마 투자할거야
- 참 환상적이구나
- I don't know. I'll probably just invest it.
- Calm down.
정말 그게 네 꿈이야?
투자하는거?
Seriously, that's your fantasy?
To invest it?
미안, 내가 투자한다고 했니?
신나게 몽땅 써버린다는 뜻이야
Oh, I'm sorry. Did I say, "invest it"?
I meant, "Be cool and piss it all away."
이렇게 하자! 우리 돈 모아서
'닉스' 팀을 사는거야!
I know! We should pool all
our money and buy the Knicks!
난 닉스팀 관심없어!
I don't really care about the Knicks.
내가 널 선발 포워드로 기용하면
관심이 생길걸?
You will when I pick you
as starting forward.
정말 그래 줄거야?
나 그런거 뽑혀본적 없어
You would do that?
I never get picked!
스포츠 팀을 사는건
별로 잘하는 일 같지 않아
I'm not sure a sports team
is the way to go.
나더러 닉스 팀을 사지 말라구?
네가 뭔데 내꿈을 망가뜨리는거야?
You won't let me buy the Knicks?
I can't believe you're taking this away.
하긴 네가 무려 15초간이나
꿈꿔온 일이지
You're right, it has been your dream
for over 15 seconds.
번호 발표하려면
얼마나 남았어요, 엄마?
How long until they announce
the numbers, Mommy?
이것도 내가 물어볼게
'엄마'?
I'll take this one too.
"Mommy"?
엠마가 옆에 있을땐
레이첼을
Oh, I've gotten into the habit
of calling Rachel..
'엄마'라고 부르는 버릇이 생겼어
"Mommy" when we're around Emma.
그러고 보니 지금은 엠마가 없네
Which I now realize we are not.
자주 들으니까 엠마가
처음하는 말도 '엄마'일거야
I'm hoping that if she hears it enough,
it'll be her first word.
그런거라면 나도
'아빠'라고 불러줘
Although if we're gonna do that,
we should probably call me "Daddy" too.
우, 그거 좋은데, 아빠?
I like that, Daddy.
레이첼한테 한말이야
I was just talking about Rachel.
아빠, 화났어?
Is Daddy getting angry?
아빠, 내 엉덩이 때릴거야?
Is Daddy gonna spank me?
글쎄, 어디볼까?
Well, that depends.
너 나쁜짓 한적..
난 도저히 못하겠다!
Have you been a bad..?
No, I can't.
여보세요?
찰리, 다른소식 없어?
Hello? Hello? Hey, Charlie.
Did anybody else hear?
뭐? 수잔이? 어떻게?
What? Susan got it? How?
나도 그 부장이랑
잠잘수 있었어!
Oh, man, I would've slept with him!
그래, 끊어!
All right, bye.
안됐다, 하지만
아직 한자리 남았잖아
Dude, I'm sorry.
But hey, there's one spot left, right?
- 찰리가 될거야
- 그런말 하지마!
- Well, Charlie's gonna get that.
- Hey, don't say that.
자기도 다른 사람들이랑
똑같이 자격이 있다구!
You've got just as good a chance
of getting that job.
찰리는 사장 아들이야
He is the boss' son.
- 로또야, 제발 당첨돼라!
- 좋아!
- Come on, lottery!
- Yeah!
- 20분 후면 번호발표야
- 다들 모여봐
- It starts in, like, 20 minutes.
- Okay, here we go.
당첨여부를 잘 알수있게
이표를 정리해야돼
We need to sort through the tickets
quickly to see if we've won.
이거 정리할 좋은 방법 없을까?
So does anybody have any ideas
how to organize this?
이건 어때?
Okay, how about this:
40장씩 여섯 묶음으로
나누는 거야
We divide them
into six groups of 40.
나머지 10장은 누구든 자기 몫
먼저 끝낸 사람이 검사하구
The remaining 10 can be read
by whoever finishes first.
- 이렇게 하면 어떨까?
- 미안, 너무 늦었어
- I have another idea.
- I'm sorry, idea time is over.
- 표는 다 이 그릇속에 있는거야?
- 그래
- Well, are all the tickets in the bowl?
- Yeah.
- 침대 옆에 있는 표는 뭐야?
- 침대옆엔 아무것도 없어!
- What about the ones on the nightstand?
- There are no tickets there.
있어, 방금전에 봤는걸
Yes, there are.
I just saw them a few minutes ago.
그럴리 없어!
자기가 착각 한거야
No, you didn't.
You must be mistaken.
- 아냐, 침대 옆에 20장쯤 있던걸?
- 내 목소리 들으면 모르겠어?
- There are 20 tickets on the nightstand.
- Chandler, sense the tone.
이런, 이 엄마가 뭘 찾았게?
Well, well, well.
Look what Mommy found.
그래! 챈들러와 내몫으로
20장 따로 더 샀어
Okay, fine. I bought 20 extra
tickets for me and Chandler.
점쟁이가 나더러
배신당할거란 말도 했어!
The psychic also said that
I would be betrayed.
기가 막힌다! 이건 우리 모두
공동으로 하는 거잖아!
I can't believe this.
I thought we were all in this together.
- 오빤 끼여든지 5분밖에 안됐잖아!
- 3분이야!
- Hey, you just got in five minutes ago!
- Three minutes ago!
그리고 그게 뭐가 중요해!
I don't know why that's important.
코네티컷에 가서 내내 너랑 함께
있었는데 대체 언제 저걸 산거야?
I was with you the whole time.
When did you even get those?
네가 비닐포장지도 안벗기고
야한잡지 읽고 있을때
When you were reading the dirty
magazines without taking off the plastic.
비법 전수해줄게
I'll show you how.
네가 따로산 로또 중에서
당첨이 되면 어떻게 되는거지?
Okay. Well, Monica, suppose one
of your special tickets wins?
로또에 당첨되고 친구들을
전부 잃은 기분이 어떨까?
How are you gonna feel when you win
and lose your friends?
당첨되면 너희들은
절대 내곁을 못 떠날걸?
Please. If I win the lottery,
you guys are not gonna leave me.
나한테 빵 한바구니만 있어도
다들 내 옆에서 안떨어지잖아!
Someone gave me muffins last week, and
I couldn't get rid of you for three days!
챈들러, 모니카한테
그러는거 아니라고 말좀 해줘!
Chandler, would you just tell her
what she did was wrong?
그래, 우리 몫을 따로 사다니
그럼 못써!
She's right. You shouldn't have
bought tickets just for us.
끝까지 들어봐
Let me finish.
하지만 내가 백수 될 마당인데
However, it doesn't look like
I'm gonna get this job..
의리가 밥먹여주냐! 다들 시끄러!
이표는 우리거야!
so I can't afford to have principles.
So screw you! The tickets are ours!
역시 내 남편이야!
There's the man I married.
네가 로또에 당첨되는 순간
All right. Believe me,
if you win the lottery..
우린 모두 널 외면할거야
it's the last you're gonna hear
from us.
좋아! 다들 떠나버려!
새 친구들 돈으로 살거야!
Fine. Don't be my friends.
I'll buy new friends.
그런 다음 너희들처럼
성형수술 하라고 돈 대줄거다!
Yeah, and then I'll pay for their plastic
surgery so they look just like you!
오! 그렇게 나온다면 좋아!
나도 내 표 챙길래!
You know what?
I want my share of the tickets.
나도 내 표 줘!
난 닉스팀 살거야!
I want my tickets too!
And I'm buying the Knicks!
스테피 그라프도 사야지!
And Steffi Graf!
내 표도 줘! 이기면
Cool. Then I want mine too!
And if I win..
당첨금 전부
안전한 채권에 투자할거야!
I'm gonna put it all
into a very low-yield bond!
안돼!
표는 전부 한군데 모아!
No. You guys, we gotta keep
all the tickets together.
아냐! 다 나눠! 그리고
No. No, we should divide them up..
내가 따로 산건 내몫이야!
내 차로 가서 샀잖아!
and I should get extra because
we used my car!
야! 따로 챙길 사람이 있다면 나지!
Hey! Hey! If anybody gets extra tickets,
it should be me!
이건 내 아이디어였다구!
- This whole thing was my idea!
- Yeah. Thanks for inventing the lottery!
그러셔? 로또 발명해줘서
참 고맙구나!
다 관둬! 내 몫이나 내놔!
Just give them to me,
and I'll split them up!
피비!
Hey, hey!
정말 더는 못 봐주겠다!
내가 해결해줄게!
God, I can't take it anymore!
I'm putting an end to this!
피비가 뛰어내리면
피비 몫은 내가 가질거야!
- Okay, if she jumps, I get her tickets!
- Wait, no, no! Hey!
피비, 안돼!
이게 뭐야! 다 그만둬!
If we're not doing this together,
we're not doing it at all.
- 로또한테 작별인사들이나 해!
- 안돼!
- Say goodbye to your tickets.
- No! No! No!
- 피비, 제발!
- 다가오지마!
Do not come any closer!
조금만 다가가면 안돼?
중요한 부분이 눌려서 그래
Can I come a little bit closer?
Valuable things are getting squished.
뭐가 더 중요해?
친구야, 돈이야?
Now, what's more important,
your friends or money?
- 친구!
- 돈!
- Friends!
- Money!
친구
Friends.
모니카, 네가 따로 산 표
어떡할거야?
Hey, Monica,
what about your extra tickets?
전부 거기 들어갔어
They're all in there.
브래지어에 숨겨둔
다섯장도 거기 넣을게
- Even these five that I hid in my bra.
- Monica!
모니카!
그래, 좋아
다들 엄청 겁먹었지?
Okay. Good. You guys were so scared.
내가 이걸 어떻게 버리겠니?
There is no way I was
gonna dump this..
맙소사! 안돼!
God! No!
모니카, 네 그릇 깨졌어!
I think I broke your bowl.
빨리 내려가! 어서!
Go! Go! Go!
길거리 뛰어다니며 로또 표를
찾아 헤매다니 멋진 밤이야!
What a beautiful night to be running
around the street, looking for tickets.
바람 때문에 더 재미있었지?
And the wind sure made it fun.
- 피비, 절반은 못찾았어!
- 그럼 어때?
- Phoebe, we lost half of them.
- So what?
당첨될 표는 이속에 있는걸
Monica, we have the winning ticket.
점쟁이가
나 당첨 될거라고 했다니까
My psychic said I was
gonna win, remember?
그 점쟁이가 어째서 비둘기에 대해선
아무말도 안했을까?
Weird your psychic didn't mention
anything about the scary pigeon.
사실 내가 어떻게 죽을지에
대해서는 얘기해줬어
As a matter of fact, she said
that's how I'm going to die.
비둘기 때문에 수선떤거
정말 미안해
So excuse me
for being a little skittish.
메시지가 두개 와있어!
회사에서 온 걸거야
There's two messages.
This could be from work.
- 틀어봐
- 알았어, 나온다
- Oh, play them.
- Okay. Here we go.
난 아까 그 비둘기인데
사과하려고 전화했어요
Hello. This is the pigeon from
the balcony calling to apologize.
그 예쁜 아가씨 손에서
로또 표 떨어뜨려서 미안해요
I shouldn't have knocked the tickets
out of the pretty lady's hand.
전부 내 잘못이에요
아가씨는 잘못 없어요, 안녕, 구구
It was all my fault.
Not hers. Bye.
사과전화하기 쉽지 않았을거야
Well, I bet that was very hard
for him to do.
챈들러, 나 찰리야
Hey, Chandler, it's Charlie.
이거다! 조용해!
This is it.
저기 말야
마지막으로 내가 뽑혔어
Listen, it turns out I got the last spot.
정말 유감이야
함께 일해서 즐거웠어
I'm really sorry, man.
It was a lot of fun working with you.
언제든 연락해
Give me a call if you want.
오, 어떡해!
Gosh, I ' m so sorry, honey.
기운내, 챈들러
Sorry, Chandler.
너무해! 산드라가 나보다
먼저 승진했을 때랑 똑같아
It is so unfair. It's like that time they
promoted Saundra over me at work.
그 여자도 랄프 로렌 친척이야?
Was she related to Ralph Lauren?
아니, 나보다 일을 훨씬 잘했어
No, she was just much better
at her job than me.
얘들아, 로또 발표할 시간이야!
You guys, the drawing's
about to start.
엠마 잠들기 전에 전화해서
We should call my mom's
and say good night to Emma..
- 잘자라고 인사할래
- 그거 좋은 생각이다
- before she goes down.
- Good idea.
많이 속상하지?
Honey, you're being really strong
about this.
자기가 얼마나 뽑히고
싶어했는지 알아
I know how badly you wanted that job.
그래, 난 자격이 있다고
생각했어
Yeah, you know, I really
thought I deserved it.
하지만 로또에 당첨되면 되지!
130번의 기회가 있잖아
But let's go win the lottery. I mean, we
still have a 130 chances to win, right?
131번이야
Hundred and thirty-one.
잘자라, 우리 아기
사랑한다
Yeah, good night, sweetheart.
I love you.
넌 이 아빠의 귀여운 딸이야
And remember,
you're Daddy's little girl.
피비 때문에 아빠란 말
쓰는게 찝찝해졌어!
Phoebe's totally ruined that for me.
엄마, 엠마 다시 바꿔줘요
Hi, Mom. Put her back on.
레이첼, 빨리와!
번호 뽑고 있어!
Rach, they're announcing
the numbers!
벌써 내 인생이
바뀌는것 같아!
My God, I can already feel
myself changing.
당첨번호입니다! 53!
Here are your official Powerball
numbers. We have 53.
- 나 있어!
- 여기도 있어!
- I've got that.
- We have one too!
좋아! 잘 나간다!
We are on the road, people!
빨리와!
Come on!
엄만 새로 한 입술 마음에 들어하지만
솔직히 난 이해가 안돼
Mom, please, I know you love your new
lips, but I can barely understand you.
우리 엠마한테
인사하게 바꿔주세요
Would you please just let me
say good night to my daughter?
다음..
행운의 숫자는 7!
And here we go.
The Powerball is seven.
잘 살펴봐!
돈벼락좀 맞아보자!
All right, check your numbers!
Make me rich.
얘들아! 우리 엠마가
You guys,
you're not gonna believe this.
방금 처음으로 말을 했어!
I was just saying good night
to Emma, and she said her first words.
- 어머나! 정말?
- 뭐라고 했는데?
- What?
- Well, what did she say?
"글리바"라고 했어!
She said, "Gleba"!
- 번호나 맞추자!
- 그래!
Make me rich!
- 굉장하지 않아?
- 그래, 굉장한 일이야
- Isn't that amazing?
- Oh, yeah. No, no, no, that's great.
왜 반응이 그렇게 미지근해?
Why aren't you more excited?
'글리바'는 단어가 아냐
Rach, gleba is not a word.
- 아니긴 왜 아냐?!
- 그럼 무슨 뜻인데?
- Well, of course it is.
- Okay. What does it mean?
내가 단어 뜻을 어떻게 다 알아!
Well, I don't know all the words.
어쨌든 내가 엠마의 첫마디를
놓치지 않아서 다행이야
You know, I'm just glad I didn't
miss my daughter's first word.
- 천만에! '글리바'는 엄연히 단어야!
- 그럼 그 단어 넣어서 문장 만들어봐
- Yes you did! Gleba is a word!
- Okay. Use it in a sentence.
좋아! '엠마가
방금 글리바라고 말했다'
Okay. Emma just said, "Gleba."
- 그건 말이 안돼!
- 좋아! 내가 찾아볼거야!
- It's not a word.
- Okay, fine. I'm gonna look it up.
그래
Okay, great.
참, 엠마가 며칠전에도
말을 했거든?
While you're at it,
she said another word the other day.
찾아보는 김에 이것도 찾아봐
Why don't you look up:
좋아, 글리바.. 글리바..
All right. Okay. Okay. Gleba.
Gleba. Gleba. Gleba!
찾았다! "균류 안쪽의 포자를
포함하고 있는 육질부분"
Here it is! "The fleshy, spore-bearing
inner mass of a certain fungi."
과학자가 될건가봐!
She's gonna be a scientist.
- 망했다! 된사람 없어?
- 없어
- Damn it. Anybody got anything?
- No.
난 아직 다 안봤어
I'm still looking through mine.
좋아! 다시 점검해봐!
Just double-checking. No.
꽝이고, 꽝이고..
No. No.
이것도 꽝이야!
No!
여보세요?
잠깐만요
Hello? Hold on.
자기회사 부장이야
It's your boss.
퇴짜놔서 미안하다는 전화겠지
The "I'm sorry I rejected you" phone call.
남자들한테 그런 전화 받는건
익숙하지 않은데?
I'm not used to getting these
from guys.
- 여보세요?
- 챈들러?
- Hey, Steve.
- Chandler, hi.
세 자리 모두 찼다는
얘기는 들었겠지?
I'm sure you've heard
we filled the three positions.
자넨 성숙하고 경험이 많아서
We felt that with your
maturity and experience..
그런 말단자리 성에 안찼을거야
you wouldn't be happy
being someone's assistant.
천만에요!
전화 받고 커피 나르고
I'd love to be somebody's
assistant. Answering phones..
그런 잡일 좋아해요!
getting coffee,
I live for that stuff.
그리고 저 아주 유치해요!
방귀! 찌찌! 똥침!
And I'm not too mature.
Farts, boobies, butt cracks!
자네는 이번 프로그램에서
가장 우수한 인턴사원이었어
Chandler, you were the strongest
person in the program.
그래서 신입 카피라이터로
채용하기로 했네
We're offering you the position
of junior copywriter.
절요? 방금 '똥침' 운운한
절 말이죠?
Me? That guy
who just said, "butt cracks"?
맞아
Yes, that's right.
자네의 세련된 궤변에
We're excited about the level
of sophistication..
벌써부터 기대가 커
you'll be bringing to the job.
고맙습니다! 열심히 할게요
내일 뵙죠
Okay. Well, thanks, you won't regret it.
I'll see you tomorrow.
왜?
What?
- 아! 나 카피라이터로 채용됐어
- 와!
Oh, yeah, I'm gonna
be a junior copywriter.
축하해!
장하다, 우리 남편!
Congratulations!
Oh, sweetie, I'm so proud of you.
고마워! 그럼 오늘밤
나 기대해도 돼?
Thanks. Does that mean
I get the good loving tonight?
물론이지!
TV고 뭐고 다 끄자!
You bet. No TV or anything.
- 진짜 잘됐다!
- 고마워
- Hey, that is so great about the job.
- Thanks, man.
너 취직하는데 내가
도움이 된것 같아 기분 좋다
I'd like to think I had
something to do with it.
- 정말? 어떻게?
- 아까 그 위시본 말야
- Really? Why?
- Well, before with the wishbone.
로또 당첨되라고 빌지 않았어
너 취직하라고 빌었어
I didn't wish we would win the lottery.
I wished you'd get the job.
정말?
Oh, yeah?
모니카한텐 말하지마
너 당장 죽이려들거야
Listen, don't tell Monica.
She'll rip your heart right out.
그거 알아?
나도 한편으로는
Well, you know what?
There was a little part of me..
우리가 정말
당첨될 거라고 생각했어
that really thought
we were gonna win.
나도 그랬어
Me too. So much for my
dinosaur/Amelia Earhart theme park.
"공룡-에어하트 테마파크"는
물 건너갔군
얘들아
행운의 숫자가 몇번이었지?
You guys? What was the Powerball
number again?
- 7
- 당첨됐다!
- Seven.
- We won.
- 뭐? 정말?
- 당첨이야!
- What?
- We won!
- 어디봐!
- 찢어지겠어!
- Let me see! Let me see!
- Don't tear it!
앞의 5자리는
하나도 맞은게 없잖아!
Phoebe, you don't have any
of the first five numbers!
알아! 하지만 행운의 숫자는 맞았잖아!
3달러 당첨됐다구!
I know that, but look, we got
the Powerball number. We won $3!
와! 20년에 걸쳐 나눠 받을래?
아니면 한번에 다 받을래?
Wow, you think we should get that over
20 years or go for the big payout?
아무렴 어때?
나 당첨되본거 처음이야! 신난다!
I don't care. I've never won
anything before. I can't believe this!
그 3달러 가지고 뭐 할거야?
So, Phoebe, what are you gonna do
with your $3?
3달러가 다 내것은 아니잖아
우리 각자 50센트씩 받게 돼
Well, it's not all mine.
We all get 50 cents.
내 50센트 너 줄께
You know what?
You can have mine.
- 나도
- Me too.
나도
Me too.
다들 그렇게 한다면야..
Well, I guess if everybody else is.
'센트럴 퍼크'
로또 안내전화 걸어봤는데
Hey, guys. So I just called
the Powerball hot line.
- 이번에 당첨자가 없대
- 내가 있잖아!
- Can you believe it? Nobody won.
- I beg to differ.
거액 당첨자는 없나보더라구
그런데 어떤 남자가 요 앞길에서
Maybe nobody won the jackpot,
but there was this guy in here earlier..
and he found a ticket on the street
right outside and won $10,000.
로또 복권 1장을 주웠는데
그게 만달러에 당첨됐대
구구, 또 나예요
예쁜 아가씨 탓하지 마세요
Again, don't blame the pretty lady.
그 아가씨 잘못이 아녜요
전부 저 비둘기의 잘못이에요, 구구
It was not her fault.
It was me, the pigeon.
제발 그 언니좀
그만 째려봐요
Seriously, stop staring at her.